CHRISTIAN BRYANT

SOFTWARE QA ENGINEER

DETAILS

ADDRESS

London United Kingdom

PHONE

+447487610571

EMAIL

cbryant1993@gmail.com

SKILLS

Java

....

SOL

.

Oracle

 \bullet \bullet \circ \circ

Management

• • 0 0 0

Selenium

. . . . 0

LANGUAGES

English

.

Spanish

• • • 0 0

HOBBIES

Music Producing Hiking

PROFILE

I am a QA Engineer with 4 years experience in the industry. With a creative insight into technology, along with the ability to use a broad selection of computing skills, I can bring an eclectic mix of attributes to the table due to working in a variety of roles and systems. Within these roles, I have learned the importance of good communication skills and the need to build and maintain successful and meaningful relationships with co-workers, managers and clients. I have also proven this by utilising my confident personality in presentation skills.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Software QA Engineer, Sparta Global

London

Feb 2018 — Apr 2020

Key responsibilities:

- Utilised java skills to get tests passing in daily automation regression packs by fixing code
- · Raised and kept track of defects
- · Provided stub solutions for other teams who needed data
- · Wrote and created automated tests based on tests written by test analyst
- Help TGR project go live with aiding End to End testing

Software QA Engineer, ASOS

London

Apr 2020 — Present

Key responsibilities:

- · Write test scenarios based on user stories provided
- · Automate new test scenarios to add to regression pack
- · Analyse regression packs for multiple test environments and fix failures
- · Provide demos to users of new features for the software
- Help and mentor junior SDET Engineers
- · Lead cross team End to End testing
- Collaborate with other team members to identify risks to product delivery and product quality

EDUCATION

BSc Computer Science, University of Brighton

Brighton

Oct 2012 — Jun 2016

Graduated with a Second class honours

COURSES

Certified Tester Foundation Level, ISTQB

Apr 2018

REFERENCES

References available upon request